[{
  "analysis":"",
  "answer":"A",
  "choices":
  [{
    "id":38,
    "content":"",
    "correct":false
  }, {
    "id":39,
    "content":"",
    "correct":false
  }, {
    "id":40,
    "content":"",
    "correct":false
  }, {
    "id":37,
    "content":"放的地方",
    "correct":true
  }],
  "department": {
    "id":1,
    "name":"WebUI"
  },
  "examPaper":null,
  "id":10,
  "stem":"方法",
  "subjectLevel": {
    "id":2,
    "name":"medium",
    "realName":"中等"
  },"subjectType": {
    "id":2,
    "name":"check",
    "realName":"复选题"
  },"topic":{
    "department":{
      "id":1,
      "name":"WebUI"
    },
    "id":8,
    "title":"git"
  },
  "uploadTime":"2016-09-26",
  "user":null
},{
  "analysis":"",
  "answer":"A",
  "choices":[{
    "id":34,
    "content":"",
    "correct":false
  },{
    "id":33,
    "content":"放的地方",
    "correct":true
  },{
    "id":35,
    "content":"",
    "correct":false
  },{
    "id":36,"content":"","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":9,"stem":"方法","subjectLevel":{"id":2,"name":"medium","realName":"中等"},"subjectType":{"id":2,"name":"check","realName":"复选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":8,"title":"git"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"","answer":"","choices":[{"id":30,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":32,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":31,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":29,"content":"","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":8,"stem":"","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"","answer":"","choices":[{"id":25,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":26,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":28,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":27,"content":"","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":7,"stem":"","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"大哥","answer":"D","choices":[{"id":23,"content":"吧","correct":false},{"id":24,"content":"打团","correct":true},{"id":22,"content":"你","correct":false},{"id":21,"content":"古风","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":6,"stem":"多发点","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"fsdfsfdsfdsfdf","answer":"","choices":[{"id":17,"content":"String      number    boolean    null   undefined    Object","correct":true},{"id":18,"content":"hfhd","correct":false},{"id":20,"content":"fsdffdsf","correct":false},{"id":19,"content":"fdf","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":5,"stem":"javasript中数据类型","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"fsdf","answer":"","choices":[{"id":14,"content":"fdf","correct":false},{"id":16,"content":"","correct":false},{"id":15,"content":"fdsf","correct":false},{"id":13,"content":"fdfds","correct":false}],"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"examPaper":null,"id":4,"stem":"fd","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":2,"name":"JavaEE"},"id":9,"title":"CoreJava"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"fsdf","answer":"","choices":[{"id":11,"content":"fds","correct":false},{"id":10,"content":"fsd","correct":false},{"id":12,"content":"fsdf","correct":false},{"id":9,"content":"fsd","correct":true}],"department":null,"examPaper":null,"id":3,"stem":"fsf","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":1,"name":"radio","realName":"单选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":2,"name":"JavaEE"},"id":9,"title":"CoreJava"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-26","user":null},{"analysis":"controller为控制器，filter为过滤器","answer":"","choices":[{"id":6,"content":"service","correct":false},{"id":5,"content":"controller","correct":true},{"id":8,"content":"filter","correct":true},{"id":7,"content":"factory","correct":false}],"department":{"id":2,"name":"JavaEE"},"examPaper":null,"id":2,"stem":"以下哪个不是angular的服务创建方式","subjectLevel":{"id":2,"name":"medium","realName":"中等"},"subjectType":{"id":2,"name":"check","realName":"复选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-21","user":null},{"analysis":"f","answer":"","choices":[{"id":1,"content":"b","correct":false},{"id":2,"content":"c","correct":false},{"id":4,"content":"e","correct":false},{"id":3,"content":"d","correct":true}],"department":{"id":2,"name":"JavaEE"},"examPaper":null,"id":1,"stem":"aaaaa","subjectLevel":{"id":1,"name":"easy","realName":"简单"},"subjectType":{"id":2,"name":"check","realName":"复选题"},"topic":{"department":{"id":1,"name":"WebUI"},"id":1,"title":"HTML"},"uploadTime":"2016-09-21","user":null}]
